<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JENNIFER LIN</title>
    <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://lin-jennifer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>JENNIFER LIN</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Jennifer Lin, 2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/media/icon_hu4799db72ccc21b5c03ae5dc4f5d5dc63_505273_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>JENNIFER LIN</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1$:$ Concepts and Measurements</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./1_Overview_Notes.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 1 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;political-science-is-a-science&#34;&gt;Political Science is a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SCIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Political Science is a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Science&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and so the study of politics (Political Science) follows many of the steps any scientist (be it a Biologist, Chemist, Physicist) would follow&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask Questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do Research and Formulate a theory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make Predictions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test Predictions with Data and Experiments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run statics and report results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share findings with the world!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Political Science, we try to model political space by asking questions and finding answers. However, models do not cover everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about models in your life. What comes to mind? Maybe toy cars, blueprints, maps, globes? Each of these try to model something of interest. Specifically, a car, a house (or whatever it is intending to build), streets in a city, and the world. Yet, each model is missing something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about a model of a house. If you are a plumber, you might only care about where the pipes are. If you are an electrician, maybe how the electric grid runs. If you are a painter, you only want to know the square footage of the walls, and if you are an interior designer, maybe just the layout of the space. Inherently, if I asked each of these roles to draw a model of a house, I will get different results. This is because models only display some parts well but not others. A model of a house from an interior designer will mean almost nothing to a plumber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is political science at its core. Social Science research only covers some aspect of the world. Any one study or any one way of measuring a concept is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; wrong. It is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; missing something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s take my research agenda as an example. I study rural political behavior. But it is a lot to write a paper on rural political behavior for the entire world. Therefore, it is only reasonable for me to break up the study of rural political behavior into several, more manageable question chunks. Here is a non-exhaustive list of more specific questions, where you can further break it down to even more specific questions if you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is &amp;ldquo;rural&amp;rdquo; and how do we measure it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What kinds of political behavior are we interested?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What perspective are we taking? (historical, recent elections, etc.?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;measurement&#34;&gt;Measurement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you want to model something in political science? What is the concept that you want to measure? What are some things we need to consider in thinking about how to measure this concept?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose we are interested in measuring someone&amp;rsquo;s feelings towards a member of the opposing party. In thinking about a way to measure someone&amp;rsquo;s feelings towards a member of the opposing party, we need to hash out:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How we define &amp;ldquo;feelings&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;opposing party&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reliability of the Measure &amp;ndash; same thing each time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validity of the Measure &amp;ndash; measures what we are intending&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A common way of measuring this concept is the feeling thermometer, where respondent rate, from a  0 to 100 scale, how warmly they feel towards members of their own or opposing party. But remember, all models are wrong! WHat does this measurement not assess? Perhaps trust? Intent to socialize? Belonging? All of these are valid and researchers have developed items to measure feelings towards opposing partisans to address each of these concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W1_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 1 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2$:$ Descriptive Statistics and Causality</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./2_Descriptives_Notes.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 2 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note&lt;/em&gt;: For all images, please refer to the PDF file above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;descriptive-statistics&#34;&gt;Descriptive Statistics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we have data, we want to know what our data look like and what story it tells. The most simple way to quickly glance at our data is using &lt;strong&gt;descriptive statistics&lt;/strong&gt; such as the mean, median and mode concepts we came to love since elementary school. These statistics are simple models of our data. But before calculating any means, medians or modes, it is important to consider the way we constructed the measurements so we know how to best build our model, however simple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose we want to model ice cream tastes of students at Northwestern. We can do this in many ways. Here are three very simple ways. To illustrate the examples that follow, I constructed a simple data set that we will use to follow along. This data set includes a hypothetical sample of 100 Northwestern Wildcats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;nominal-scales&#34;&gt;Nominal Scales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominal scales&lt;/strong&gt; are categorical. In survey questions, they represent items that sort into categories, often descriptive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is your favorite ice cream flavor?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chocolate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vanilla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mint Chocolate Chip&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strawberry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These data are often described using a bar graph or a pie chart. Given the small number of categories, you are likely better off just summarizing them in a table. Nonetheless, here is a bar graph of our results&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ordinal-scales&#34;&gt;Ordinal Scales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the case of &lt;strong&gt;ordinal scales&lt;/strong&gt;, we are interested in questions that generate an ordered scale as the response options. These can include items such as &amp;ldquo;From a scale of 0 - 10, how much do you like ice cream?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Do you agree or disagree with the notion that ice cream is a good desert?&amp;rdquo; For our ice cream example, here is a question to consider. The options range from &amp;ldquo;Strongly disagree&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Strongly agree&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you agree or disagree with the fact that Vanilla Ice Cream is your favorite ice cream flavor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strongly Disagree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disagree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neither Agree nor Disagree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strongly Agree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can summarize these results in a similar way that we did the nominal results. Alternatively, we can cover them to numbers and generate means and medians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interval-scales&#34;&gt;Interval Scales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;strong&gt;Interval Scales&lt;/strong&gt; are scales that use a numeric interval in the response options. Often, these have a meaningful zero and the numbers are evenly spaced apart. When you ask your friend what the temperature is outside, they likely will give you a number on the Celsius or Fahrenheit scales that both have meaningful zeros^[I guess the Celsius more so than Fahrenheit since $0^{\circ}\text{C}$ is the freezing point of water.]. When you buy something, the cashier would measure the amount you owe in dollars and cents, where there is also a meaningful zero. In our ice cream study, we can consider the following question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How many scoops of ice cream do you eat each day?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of the graphs, we can better understand our data with means and medians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-to-causality&#34;&gt;Introduction to Causality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-basics&#34;&gt;The Basics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a hot summer day, we can reasonably expect ourselves to become dehydrated, or our ice cream to melt almost instantly. Here, we are able to pinpoint direct causes of effects that we want to observe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, social science is not always as straightforward. If a tree fell in the woods, and no one was there to witness it, (a) do we know it fell and (b) can we reasonably make suggestions as to how it fell?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Causal inference is about pinpointing, with &lt;em&gt;pretty good&lt;/em&gt; certainty, how the tree fell. It is drawing a direct relationship between two variables X and Y. Notice the emphasis on &lt;em&gt;pretty good&lt;/em&gt;. This is because we cannot gain a full sense of cause in social science research, due to the error or noise that is bound to arise in human behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s turn to a case study on voting. Why do people go vote? Can it be based on any of the following?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in politics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the candidates and issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to make a change in the community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tagging along with friends and family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why not?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But at the same time, can any of these be an effect of voting?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-four-questions&#34;&gt;The Four Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using our voting example, let&amp;rsquo;s focus on the &amp;ldquo;Desire to make change in the community&amp;rdquo; aspect. Can this desire lead people to vote?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is there a relationship between X and Y?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; For voting, sure! Desires to make change leads to voting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could Y cause X?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Can voting lead to greater desires to make change? Likely, since you now began a journey of political engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is there a causal pathway from X to Y?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Likely, if we design a model to isolate the correct variables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could there be confounding variables?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; OH&amp;hellip; ABSOLUTELY!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;experiments&#34;&gt;Experiments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experiments are one of the best ways to identify causal mechanisms. You create two comparable groups using random assignment, give one group the treatment and another no treatment. Now, the only difference between the groups is the treatment, since both groups are, in theory, comparable (or the same).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
Y_{i, T} \ = \ \text{Treatment}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
Y_{i, C} \ = \ \text{Control}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\text{Causal Effect} \ = \ Y_{i, T} - Y_{i, C}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose we want to know whether &lt;strong&gt;desire to effect change&lt;/strong&gt; in society really causes &lt;strong&gt;voter turnout&lt;/strong&gt;. We con conduct an experiment using the following conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$Y_{i, T}$: Prime Desire to Effect Change in society by telling people about things in their neighborhood that need to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$Y_{i, C}$: Control message &amp;ndash; Recycling is good for the planet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a desire to effect change causes turnout, then the treatment conditions will see a higher turnout rate than the control condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W2_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 2 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3$:$ Sampling and Surveys</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./3_Sampling_Notes.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 3 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-you-want-to-conduct-a-survey&#34;&gt;So you want to Conduct a Survey?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-you-need&#34;&gt;What you need&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To run a good survey, you need some of the following&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;RANDOM&lt;/strong&gt; Sample&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Survey Questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills to analyze survey data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, we will focus on the &lt;strong&gt;Random&lt;/strong&gt; Sample component&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-random-what-is-a-sample&#34;&gt;What is Random? What is a Sample?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, what is a &lt;strong&gt;sample&lt;/strong&gt;? To figure that out, we need to know what is part of the &lt;strong&gt;population&lt;/strong&gt;, or the entire entity of the thing that we are interested in studying. Individuals or single unites in the population constitute our &lt;strong&gt;unit of analysis&lt;/strong&gt;. This can be people (a person), states (a state), or households (house).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When designing a study, your &lt;strong&gt;sample&lt;/strong&gt; is a selection of the units in the population and it should resemble the entire group of interest. There are many ways to pick a sample and there are positives and negatives of each method&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sampling of Convenience&lt;/strong&gt;: Select cases that are easily accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a. EXAMPLE: Stand outside of dining hall and interview everyone trying to go in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b. EXAMPLE: Polls on FOX, CNN, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quota Samples&lt;/strong&gt; are where you modify the convenience sample to make it more like the population&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a. This is also known as &lt;strong&gt;non-probability sampling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b. This is often used in online survey marketplaces and Amazon Mechanical Turk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c. EXAMPLE: The COVID States Project: &lt;a href=&#34;https://covidstates.org/&#34;&gt;https://covidstates.org/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
- We want to know political attitudes and behaviors of people in each US State &lt;br&gt;
- We conduct online samples to get respondents from each US State &lt;br&gt;
- Each state has a quota of 300-500 per wave, depending on size.&lt;br&gt;
- Within each state, we do race, gender and age cross tabs so that each bucket gets a fix number equivalent to their percent in the state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Sampling&lt;/strong&gt; is where each case has an equal and known probability of being selected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a. Also known as &lt;strong&gt;Probability Sampling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b. Often done by Random Digit Dialing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c. EXAMPLE: Kaiser Family Foundation (Random Digit Dialing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d. &lt;strong&gt;Law of Large Numbers&lt;/strong&gt;: Random Sampling gives us a good approximation of the population with a large enough population&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e. Types of Random Samples:&lt;br&gt;
1. &lt;strong&gt;Simple Random Sample&lt;/strong&gt;: Each person has the same probability of being included.&lt;br&gt;
2. &lt;strong&gt;Cluster Sample&lt;/strong&gt;: Group participants into meaningful subgroups and select the subgroup to its entirety.&lt;br&gt;
3. &lt;strong&gt;Stratified Random Sampling&lt;/strong&gt;: Group participants into meaningful subgroups and select samples from the subgroup where EACH member of the subgroup has the same probability of selection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;issues-with-surveys&#34;&gt;Issues with Surveys&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surveys may have multiple issues related to measurements. For the sampling front, however, we are interested in issues with the sample recruitment. Some issues here might include&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Non-response&lt;/strong&gt;: People selected for the survey just don&amp;rsquo;t want to engage with the survey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hard to Reach Populations&lt;/strong&gt;: Some people who are selected for surveys might not be able to access the survey OR it can be hard to reach some people since they are difficult to identify.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are some ways to address these issues. But to do this, we need to be creative with our sampling methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snowball Sampling&lt;/strong&gt;: Getting potential participants from current participants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respondent-driven Sampling&lt;/strong&gt;: Go where the participants are (or might be)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W3_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 3 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4$:$ Surveys, Experiments, Midterms and More</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./4_Review_NOTES.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 4 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;writing-a-good-survey-question&#34;&gt;Writing a Good Survey Question&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surveys are often built to compare groups, describe something or analyze something. Survey questions are designed for you to be able to ask people about their attitudes and behaviors on certain topics. As such, people are self-reporting the information through the questions that you pose to them. Writing a good survey question can be rather difficult as you need to consider and ask about the who, what, when, where, why and how of the situation. There are so many things to think about and there are often space limitations so the struggle is getting the questions out and fitting it into the framework set by your resource limitations (i.e. time, length of the survey etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore, when writing a survey question, there are few things that we need to think about. First, it is important for you to put yourself in the shoes of the participant. So how do participants answer survey questions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 0: Encode Information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 1: Understand all the words and what the question is asking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 2: Recall all information and figure out how to answer the question&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 3: Assess initial answer for accuracy and completeness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 4: Report answer by mapping your answer to the options given&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the process of putting yourself in your participants&#39; shoes, you should also think about the difficulty of the question and whether the understand the issues that you are talking about. (For example, do not ask about an obscure TV show if you know they are likely not watching it.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, your questions should address one thing per question. Therefore, if you are interested in cars, do not ask people if cars should be faster and more energy efficient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, questions that are simpler are better and they should not make assumptions of knowledge. Make sure wording is clear and the language is easy to interpret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;experiments&#34;&gt;Experiments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;fundamental problem of causal inference&lt;/strong&gt; is that we can’t compare a world with the cause to a world without the cause. Therefore, we use &lt;strong&gt;experiments&lt;/strong&gt; to solve this issue. In an experiment, we create two comparable groups using &lt;strong&gt;random assignment&lt;/strong&gt; and present one group with a treatment and another without. To be successful, the groups that result from random assignment should be relatively large and should reflect an independent selection process from the population, where each member had an equal chance of inclusion. This essentially creates a situation where we can study the treatment and control at the same time. There are several kinds of experiments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lab experiments&lt;/strong&gt;: Experiments are conducted in a lab or another controlled setting. For example, you can bring participants to the lab to test the effect of deliberation on political attitudes on various issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field experiments&lt;/strong&gt;: Experiments are conducted in the natural environment but stimuli are controlled &amp;ndash; examples include going to neighborhoods and exposing people to treatments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Natural experiments&lt;/strong&gt;: Taking advantage of a comparative scenario between at least two groups and letting that be the treatment and control and observe the effect. For example, if you wanted to compare the effect of an earthquake on happiness, you can conduct a natural experiment comparing two towns, one hit by an earthquake and one that did not and see how it affected feelings of the people there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey experiments&lt;/strong&gt;: Experiments that are done via surveys. The treatments are comparable to survey questions, but participants are often asked to read, listen, watch, write, or respond to some questions that serve as the treatment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In experiments, we are concerned with two kinds of validity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Internal Validity&lt;/strong&gt;: Does the treatment cause the dependent variable in this study?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Validity&lt;/strong&gt;: Does the treatment generalize across persons, settings, treatment variables and measurement variables? In other words, are the findings generalize in some way?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W4_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 4 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6$:$ Confidence Intervals</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./6_Confidence_NOTES.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 6 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;observational-studies-and-large-n-methods&#34;&gt;Observational Studies and Large N Methods&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, we want to study things where we cannot randomly assign participants to the independent variable. In that case, we can only conduct &lt;strong&gt;observational studies&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Observational Studies&lt;/strong&gt; are research projects where we don&amp;rsquo;t assign values to the independent variable. We just see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some examples of these projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does living in a rural area predict conservative political attitudes?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are some reasons that people are not getting the COVID-19 vaccine?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do people perceive others who are vaccinated or not vaccinated?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To analyze the data in observational studies, we often require large N statistical methods. These are statistics tests that we use to analyze observational studies. For these methods, we care about the &lt;strong&gt;population&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;parameter&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;sample&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;statistic&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;population-parameters&#34;&gt;Population Parameters&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Parameters&lt;/em&gt; are aspects of the population that we care about. They are often denoted using Greek letters ( $\mu$, $\pi$, $\alpha$, $\beta$). They capture something that is true for the entire population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some examples of this include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Examples&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total number of registered Republicans and Democrats in the United States&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total number of people in the US who love vanilla ice cream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, remember that it is difficult to study the entire population. Think back to the week on survey deign and sampling. We cannot expect to ask everyone in the population. Therefore, we can only expect to &lt;strong&gt;estimate&lt;/strong&gt; the population parameters &lt;em&gt;using statistics&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;statistics&#34;&gt;Statistics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Statistics&lt;/em&gt; are estimates of the population using data that we gather from a subset of the population. We collect the samples using the sampling methods discussed earlier in the quarter (remember: Probability versus nonprobability sampling?). We can calculate sample statistics like mean from the sample and use them to predict the population. Sample statistics are usually denoted by letters (p, a, b).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question then becomes: How do we know how &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; our predictions are? To answer this question, think back to the first week when we discussed models in this section. Remember that models are inherently missing something. Sampling statistics are models of the population. So how do we know how correct our models are especially since each of the sampling methods can be imperfect? We can use &lt;strong&gt;confidence Intervals&lt;/strong&gt;, which signals how &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; we are about our predictions. They show us a range of values [lower, upper] that is possible for the population parameter to lie given the findings from our sample. The most common confidence interval is the 95%, which shows that we are confident that the true population parameter (usually mean) is within the bounds of the calculated range 95% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some ways to remember the gist of a confidence interval:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When calculating confidence intervals, you are casting a net for the true population mean. Therefore, the wider the net you cast, the more likely you are to get it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When calculating confidence intervals, you are opening an umbrella to keep yourself dry in a rainstorm. The larger the umbrella, the more likely it is that you keep yourself dry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;calculating-confidence-intervals&#34;&gt;Calculating Confidence Intervals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To calculate a confidence interval, we need three pieces of information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The mean (or parameter of interest)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The sample size&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The confidence percentage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-confidence-percentage&#34;&gt;The Confidence Percentage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to determine how wide of a net to cast to ensure success. Traditionally, this is 95%. But, we can have other percentages as well. From there, we need to get our corresponding z-score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Percent&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;z-score&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;90%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;1.65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;95%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;1.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;99%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;2.57&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-mean-or-any-other-sample-statistic&#34;&gt;The Mean (or any other sample statistic)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For means, we can compute this as we usually compute averages from sample statistics^[For means, this is often denoted as $\overline{x}$]. Essentially, this component is a descriptive statistic that we derive from the sample we have drawn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-standard-error&#34;&gt;The Standard Error&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The standard error is the standard deviation of the sampling distribution. This is based on the sample size and is computed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
SE = \sqrt{\frac{p \times (1 - p)}{N}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;confidence-interval&#34;&gt;Confidence Interval&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pulling this together, the way we calculate a confidence interval is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\overline{x} \pm z(\sqrt{\frac{p \times (1 - p)}{N}})
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-example-of-how-to-calculate-a-confidence-interval&#34;&gt;An Example of How to Calculate a Confidence Interval&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose I polled a sample of Northwestern students to whether or not the approve of the quarter system. I want to predict whether the entire population of students approve the quarter system over the semester system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To do this, I polled 40 students outside of the Norris University Center. I get the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mean: .75 say they approve of the quarter system&lt;br&gt;
N: 40&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to compute a 95% Confidence Interval&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I calculate the standard error&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
SE = \sqrt{\frac{.75 \times (1 - .75)}{40}} \approx 0.06846532
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, I plug it into the broader equation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 1.96(0.06846532)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 0.134192
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the result is&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
[0.615808, 0.884192] \ \text{or} \ [0.62, 0.88]
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bow, suppose I take the same condition but I want to estimate a 90% confidence interval. Here, I can use the same standard error (since no part of that has changed) and rewrite the calculations as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 1.65(0.06846532)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 0.1129678
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
[0.6370322, 0.8629678] \ \text{or} \ [0.63, 0.86]
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we can see, the interval in the 90% is smaller than the 95% since we are casting a smaller net.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, now I am interested in calculating a 99% confidence interval. I can use the same conditions as I have before and rerun the math. Here is how that looks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 2.57(0.06846532)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 0.1759559
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
[0.5740441, 0.9259559] \ \text{or} \ [0.57, 0.93]
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice that, compared to the 95% interval, this interval is wider and this is because we have casted a bigger net.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing up the scenario, suppose I am interested in the same question as before but instead of sampling 40 students, I have sampled 400 students outside of Norris instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find the same 95% confidence interval, I can follow the same steps as before, starting with the standard error calculations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
SE = \sqrt{\frac{.75 \times (1 - .75)}{400}} \approx 0.02165064
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then, we can continue the calculations by plugging everything into the main equation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 1.96(0.02165064)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
.75 \pm 0.04243525
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
[0.7075647, 0.7924353] \ \text{or} \ [0.70, 0.79]
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice that, with the bigger sample, even on the same confidence level, our confidence interval closes around the mean. This is because a larger sample allows us to get a better sense of the population, making it a more precise estimate (as opposed to accurate since we are still not sure if our sample is actually good at capturing the true mean.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W6_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 6 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7$:$ Regression</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./7_Regression_NOTES.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 7 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See PDF for figures &amp;ndash; this is a figure heavy handout &amp;ndash; a separate HTML file can be provided upon request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W7_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 7 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8$:$ Qualitative Research Methods</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/courses/ps210/week8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handout&#34;&gt;Handout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./8_Qualitative_NOTES.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 8 Handout (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Up until this point, we have largely focused on large-N and quantitative research methods including descriptive statistics, experiments, surveys, confidence intervals and regressions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, we now turn to small-N and qualitative research methods. These methods are based on text-based data and you study a small number of cases in great detail. Data analysis is based on finding patterns in the process or entity of interest. Common types of qualitative methods include&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Historical Methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-Depth Interviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus Groups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participant Observation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;historical-methods&#34;&gt;Historical Methods&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Historical Methods are based primarily based on primary source research methods where you look at documents stored in archives and draw conclusions based on these documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A subfield in American politics that is built off of the historical methods, primary source approach is &lt;strong&gt;American Political Development (APD)&lt;/strong&gt;, which studies that continuity and change over time in American politics, including how the state was built and how society, and its institutions, has changed across the years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An example of a study that uses the APD method is Lacombe (2019). In this paper, Lacombe is interested in the way the the NRA develops a social identity among their members and how they can use this social identity to mobilize their membership base in political action. To do this, he coded 79 years of the &lt;em&gt;American Rifleman&lt;/em&gt; magazine and letters to the editor in major American newspapers and conducts content analyses of these letters and entries. The results show that the NRA created and channeled a social identity in all resources to build influence in mass arenas and that this identity is powerful in mobilizing the membership base in political action. It has become more powerful over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;interviews&#34;&gt;Interviews&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interviews are based on conversations with subjects or groups of interest. Types of interviews include&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Structured Interviews&lt;/strong&gt;: Provide a set number of questions for each participant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unstructured Interviews&lt;/strong&gt;: Broad topics for conversations and depending on the answers, you respond flexibly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semi-Structured Interviews&lt;/strong&gt;: A mix of questions and free flowing discussions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;focus-groups&#34;&gt;Focus Groups&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another type of qualitative research method that stems out of interviews are &lt;strong&gt;focus groups&lt;/strong&gt;. These are centered around a group of people who discuss a topic moderated by a facilitator. The goal is often to arrive at a solution of a issue, evaluate a program, understanding concepts etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collectively, interviews and focus groups happen more in sociology than in political science. Common topics of focus groups I have seen include experiences of the LGBTQIA+ peoples in various social groups such as civic organizations and churches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;participant-observation&#34;&gt;Participant Observation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Participant Observation&lt;/strong&gt;, or &lt;strong&gt;ethnography&lt;/strong&gt;, is a research method where researchers go to the community, join the group and observe their behavior without being too actively involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One example of this research method is Cramer (2012). In this paper, she was interested in why people vote against their self-interests and use rural Americans as a case study. People in rural America tend to be poor and less educated, which makes their policy interests align more with the agenda of the Democrats. However, they do not vote for the Democrats. To find out why, Cramer visited 37 regularly congregating discussion groups in coffee shops and bookstores across 27 communities across Wisconsin between May 2007 and May 2011. She observed and recorded their conversations to learn about their attitudes about politics without intervening in their conversations. her results emphasized the importance of group consciousness in personal political decisionmaking. Rural Americans collectively despise urban Americans as they blame the urban residents and politicians from urban areas for all of their problems. Therefore, they vote against the Democrat party, who champions city interests and whose politicians are more likely from cities than small towns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-qualitative-meets-quantitative&#34;&gt;Where Qualitative meets Quantitative&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Text as Data&lt;/strong&gt; methods take qualitative data and quantify it to meaningful data that we can use statistical methods to analyze. Texts are treated as a &amp;ldquo;bag of words&amp;rdquo; to analyze using dictionaries. This allows us to find patterns in large sums of text without necessarily needing to read each text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An example of this combination of qualitative and quantitative method is a paper that I have been working on. In this paper, I wanted to investigate whether Democrats and Republicans appeal to different moral values and to what extent they align with the moral values that are championed by their base. Past research has suggested that Democrats and Republicans appeal to different moral values in their press releases, church sermons, and platforms. So for this study, I was interested in national conventions, which are focused on getting voters excited for the election and willing to mobilize on the party&amp;rsquo;s behalf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this project, my methods are summarized as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect transcripts of speeches delivered at the Democrat and Republican National Convention from 2008 to 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parse data using the Moral Foundations Dictionary with text as data methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code data based on the definitions of the foundations to see how well the dictionary does in sorting the moral appeals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This provides me with both qualitative and quantitative data to work with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the qualitative data, we can draw parallel conclusions as the quantitative data. For example, the Harm foundation is interested in caring and protecting vulnerable peoples. This is a core value of the Democrat party. The dictionary characterized Bernie Sanders&#39; 2020 Democrat National Convention speech as a good example of appeals to the Harm foundation. If we read the speech, we can see why&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As long as I am here, I will work with progressives, with moderates, and yes, with conservatives to preserve this nation from a threat that so many of our heroes fought and died to defeat. This president is not just a threat to our democracy, but by rejecting science, he has put our lives and health in jeopardy. Trump has attacked doctors and scientists trying to protect us from the pandemic while refusing to take strong action to produce the masks, gowns, and gloves our healthcare workers desperately need. Nero fiddled while Rome burned. Trump golfs. His actions fanned this pandemic resulting in over 170,000 deaths and a nation still unprepared to protect its people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As another example, the Authority foundation emphasizes traditions, rule of law, and respect for authority. This is a core value for the Republican party and the text methods coded the speech by Rudy Giuliani in the 2020 Republican National Convention as a good example of appeals to this value. The excerpt of his speech seem to parallel this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is clear that a vote for Biden and the Democrats creates the risk that you will bring this lawlessness to your city, to your town, to your suburb. There is no question that this awesome job of restoring safety for our people cannot be done from your basement, Joe. There&amp;rsquo;s also no question that President Trump will fight with all his strengths to preserve the American system of government and our way of life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the parties do appeal to different moral values but I also find that they use the value systems of the opposite party to mobilize moderate and swing voters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This study, and the others that I showed you in this section, demonstrate the use to qualitative data in Political Science research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./W8_Slides.pdf&#34;&gt;Week 8 Slides (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Rural Attitudes Just Republican?</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/republican_psrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/republican_psrm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Political Consequences of Depression$:$ How Conspiracy Beliefs, Participatory Inclinations, and Depression Affect Support for Political Violence</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/depression_ajps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/depression_ajps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban-Rural Differences in Non-Voting Political Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/nonvotingprq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/nonvotingprq/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prevalence of Firearm Ownership Among Individuals With Major Depressive Symptoms</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/firearmjama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/firearmjama/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association of Major Depressive Symptoms With Endorsement of COVID-19 Vaccine Misinformation Among US Adults</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/vaxmisinfojama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/vaxmisinfojama/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association Between Social Media Use and Self-reported Symptoms of Depression in US Adults</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/socialmediajama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/socialmediajama/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using General Messages to Persuade on a Politicized Scientific Issue</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/vax_messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/vax_messages/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 61$:$ Parental Concerns about COVID-19 Vaccines</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr61/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr61/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 59$:$ What Americans Think About People Who Are Not Vaccinated</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr59/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr59/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender-specificity of Resilience in Major Depressive Disorder</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/gender_da/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/gender_da/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persistence of Symptoms up to 10 Months Following Acute COVID-19 Illness</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/persist_covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/persist_covid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 51$:$ Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in California</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr51/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ Understanding Attitudes and Behaviors during the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/ncfmay2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/ncfmay2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../NCFMay2021.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Barack Obama to Donald Trump$:$ The Evolution of Moral Appeals in National Conventions</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/convmpsa21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/convmpsa21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 44$:$ Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in Massachusetts</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr44/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr44/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 42$:$ Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in New York</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr42/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr42/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 41$:$ Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr41/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 30$:$ Economic Hardships Due to the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr30/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 27$:$ The Trajectory of Health-Related Behaviors in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr27/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Functions for Northwestern University Political Science Methods Classes</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/polstat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/polstat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Purpose: Helpful functions and data to use with the Northwestern University PS 403 course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The functions here were originally part of the &lt;code&gt;lin&lt;/code&gt; package but are moved to facilitate a clearer definition of package propose and contents. Since the &lt;code&gt;lin&lt;/code&gt; package features commands I often use, some of these functions do not fit that category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Functions in this package are meant to facilitate the understanding of core statistics concepts covered in introductory policial science methods courses. They might be useful in research in the long term but R often has a better and more appropriate means for executing those duties than the functions provided here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This package may be useful to a more general audience, however, current students of PS 403 are NOT encouraged to download this until AFTER they completed the class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;library(devtools)
install_github(&amp;quot;lin-jennifer/polstat&amp;quot;)
library(polstat)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 21$:$ Most Important Problems Facing the Country Today</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Lin&#39;s Collection of Functions</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/lin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This package contains my most used commands and R features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may not be the most useful for the general public, but may be necessary if you are collaborating with me or interacting with my R code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;library(devtools)
install_github(&amp;quot;lin-jennifer/lin&amp;quot;)
library(lin)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask Only What Your Country Can Do for You$:$ Group Interests, Constituency Characteristics, and Demands for Representation</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/demands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/demands/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Polarization and COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/ap-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/ap-covid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation$:$ A 50-State COVID-19 Survey, Report 13$:$ Public Trust in Instutions and Vaccine Acceptance</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/csr13/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Nation -- A 50-State Survey of COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/research/covidstates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/research/covidstates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;published-materials&#34;&gt;Published Materials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-reports&#34;&gt;Data Reports&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reprots indicated with $^{*}$ indicates reports that I led, co-led or oversaw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 12: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/vj45t/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Executive Approval Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 13$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/qzsxn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Trust and Vaccine Acceptance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 14: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/w974j/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Misinformation and Vaccine Acceptance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 15: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/s7jgt/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Support for a Fifth COVID-19 Relief Package&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 16: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/wrj4b/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Partisan Differences in Intention to Vote by Mail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 17: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/rz34x/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Test Result Times&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 19: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/tcefb/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Pandemic-related Factors Associated with Candidate Preferences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 20: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/gz29a/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Opinion Around Federal and State Reactions to COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 21$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/q3av7/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Most Important Problems Facing the Nation Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 22: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/z3652/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Executive Approval Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 23: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/3s8v4/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Depression Among Young Adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 24: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/kchn8/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;The Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 25: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/8pcyn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Support for Measures Aimed at Curbing COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 26: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/37jbe/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Covid-19-related Behaviors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 27$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/27gqm/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Covid-19-related Behaviors in Illinois&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 28: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/j5pzh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Support for Measures Aimed at Curbing COVID-19 in Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 29: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/j8v3u/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Election Fairness and Trust in Institutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 30: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/jb6sk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Economic Hardships Due to the COVID-19 Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 31: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/qpkvy/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on the Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 32: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/svf4w/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on Public Support for Measures Aimed at Curbing COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 33: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/zkgvc/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on COVID-19 Test Turnaround Times Across the Country&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 34: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/v29s7/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on Holiday Gatherings in December 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 35: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/xtykv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Attitudes Towards COVID-19 Vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 36: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/d36nh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Evaluation of COVID-19 Vaccine Communication Strategies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 37: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/fmrqp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Gun Purchases During the COVID-19 Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 38: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/uprg2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Perceptions of Education During the COVID-19 Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 39: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/3qfs9/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Attitudes Towards the Storming of the Capitol Building&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 40: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/p4q9h/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes Among Healthcare Workers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 41$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/8w7zy/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 42$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/ywk4a/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in New York&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 43: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/rnw8z/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Vaccine Rates and Attitudes Among Americans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 44: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/yhtn3/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 45: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/e95bc/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vaccine Hesitancy and Resistance Among Parents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 46: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/shveq/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Executive Approval Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 47: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/a352z/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes Among Healthcare Workers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 48: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/j5hf2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Assessing the Impact of the Pause in Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson Vaccine Use on COVID-19 Vaccination Intent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 49: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/stacj/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vaccinating America&amp;rsquo;s Youth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 50: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/vdgj4/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update on the Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson Vaccine Pause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 51$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/bas8w/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trajectory of Health-related Behaviors in California&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 52: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/pnqr4/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Support for Vaccine Requirements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 53: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/5zkuv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Public Support for Vaccine Passports&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 54: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/cgfzt/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Mental Health in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 55: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/pfxnv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Social Isolation During the COVID-19 Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 56: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/fwker/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vaccine Resistance Among Parents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 57: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/uvqbs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Social Media News Consumption and COVID-19 Vaccination Rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 58: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/6wcn9/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;High Public Support for Mandating Vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 59$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/fy6jz/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;What Americans Think About People Who Are Not Vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 60: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/xtjad/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vaccine misinformation: From uncertainty to resistance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report 61$^{*}$: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osf.io/c2xmj/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Parental concerns about COVID-19 vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library of Political Texts (poltextr)</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/poltextr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/poltextr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;IMG src=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/poltextr.png&#34; align=right border=20px HSPACE=”50” VSPACE=”50”&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To easily access any textual data that I use in my research in R, I created an R package that stores the corpuses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;library(devtools)
install_github(&amp;quot;lin-jennifer/poltextr&amp;quot;)
library(poltextr)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;access-data&#34;&gt;Access Data&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see which datasets are available in the package, run the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;data(package=&amp;quot;poltextr&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this package, metadata files contain details about the speakers and they are labelled with &lt;code&gt;_meta&lt;/code&gt; at the end of the data name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To load a corpus, run&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;data(dnc16) # Loads DNC speeches from 2016
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Metadata files are loaded in as &lt;code&gt;.csv&lt;/code&gt; files and can be called as a data frame by running&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;data(dnc16_meta) # Loads DNC metadata from 2016
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;library-contents&#34;&gt;Library Contents&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;national-convention-speeches&#34;&gt;National Convention Speeches&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;years-included-and-parties&#34;&gt;Years Included (and Parties)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020 (Democrat and Republican)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016 (Democrat and Republican)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;political-party-platforms&#34;&gt;Political Party Platforms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feature is Still in the Works&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;categories&#34;&gt;Categories&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Democrat Party Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Republican Party Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;presidential-debates&#34;&gt;Presidential Debates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feature is Still in the Works&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;election-years&#34;&gt;Election Years&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applying to Graduate School</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/post/applying-to-graduate-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/post/applying-to-graduate-school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I applied to 12 Political Science Ph.D. programs during my senior year as an undergraduate student, most of them in the Midwest, and I got accepted to 7 of them. This process, especially as a first-generation college student, was challenging for me. Fortunately, I had great mentors in the process&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. I wanted to take this opportunity to discuss some of the experiences that I had, things that worked for me, and opportunities that aspiring graduate students can take advantage of in their journeys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post assumes that you have already determined which programs that you are going to apply to. For Political Science, most applications entail applying to the department, which means that learning about the opportunities and work that current faculty and graduate students there do can be a good place to start compiling the list of programs. In picking programs, approach this with purpose &amp;ndash; think about some reach programs, some target and some safety that might work for you. It can also help to know the network of your &lt;a href=&#34;#LOR&#34;&gt;letter writers&lt;/a&gt; and use that to inform your search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt; I am not a professional advisor for graduate school application. I am largely speaking for my experience going through this process with reasonable success&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Main&#34;&gt;Main Components&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#GRE&#34;&gt;The GRE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#GPA&#34;&gt;Transcripts and GPA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#WS&#34;&gt;Writing Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#CV&#34;&gt;CV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#LOR&#34;&gt;Letters of Recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#SOP&#34;&gt;Statement of Purpose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#OMS&#34;&gt;Opportunities for Minority Students&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Fee&#34;&gt;Application Fee Waiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Visit&#34;&gt;Diversity Visit Weekends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Main&#34;&gt;Components of the Graduate Application&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the program, there may be some differences in the exact requirements of the application. However, there are 6 main sections that generally apply across most Ph.D. applications, certainly in Political Science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;GRE&#34;&gt;The GRE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My best advice: take it once &lt;em&gt;when you feel confident and ready&lt;/em&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a 4 hour computer-based test and costs $205 &amp;ndash; In other words, it is long, expensive and an experience that is best when had only once. I recognize that, by saying this, it assumes that you have the luxury of time to choose when it is best for you to test. Since you can test anytime until mid-November of Fall semester, which is basically 3 weeks before most applications are due, it is possible that you might be in a situation where you just have to do it to get the best possible score for this cycle&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And to be clear, I &lt;strong&gt;do not&lt;/strong&gt; recommend waiting until the last mintue to test. Many people have told me that testing during Spring or Summer of your junior year may be a good option. When considering when you should take your GRE, look at your calendar and ballpark a date. Unlike the SATs and ACTs for high school, GRE test slots are available almost every day of the week with many places near you that can administer the test.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; As a result, it is up to you to plan for a time that is most comfortable and a time you feel most prepared to test.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparing for the Test&lt;/strong&gt;: Other than planning on when/where to take the test, I highly recomment preparing for the test itself. On social media, I have seen numerous advice boards where people say that, if you are good in English or math, you can just test without a problem. Even if you are a math geek or have an broad vocabulary, I still recommend going through a practice guide to work out the problems and taking a few practice tests using &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ets.org/gre/revised_general/prepare/powerprep/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PowerPrep Plus&lt;/a&gt;, which is ETS&amp;rsquo;s test similator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing with Accommodations&lt;/strong&gt;: If you have ADA accommodations through your college/workplace, I highly recommend applying them for the GRE. To apply, consult the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ets.org/gre/revised_general/register/disabilities&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Accommodations for Test Takers with Disabilities or Health-related Needs&lt;/a&gt; for more information. As the page suggests, this process takes some time, which means that it would require more planning on your end to detwemine when you want to take the test and submit documentation with ample time to ensure that everything gets processed in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;GPA&#34;&gt;Transcripts and GPA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each graduate program has different requirements for how to submit a transcript. Most of them require a scan of an official transcript and only want sealed copies once you confirm that you are attending their program. Others might require mailed copies in the application process and still others might ask for a sealed copy in order to send you an acceptance letter. Understanding the transcript requirements early on can save you some money in the process. I recommend reading through the requirements for all your programs to best plan for when to order, the number of copies to order, and where to send them. By default, you should plan to order one scan copy for all the applications and add to reflect the differences in application requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schools without GPAs&lt;/strong&gt;: If you attend a college without a GPA, as I did, reach out to the Director of Graduate Studies (DGS) or Graduate Coordinator of your intended program(s) and ask about how you should go about filling out the GPA field. In your email, you should also ask about how you can submit any documents that reflect course performance. In my case, it was narrative evaluations that, fortunately, were part of my transcript so I sent a massive file with all of those documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;WS&#34;&gt;Writing Sample&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Writing Sample is your opportunity to demonstrate competence in research skills. When selecting your sample, consider a piece that accurately captures your research interests and showcases your ability to collect data, run analyses, and communicate your findings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advice that I got in this step was to take care of each section because you would not know which section the admissions committee would read. They might read the entire paper, they might read a section, they might skim &amp;ndash; either way, it is not a document where you want typos hanging around. In other words, if you are submitting a final paper from a class last year, be sure to still read it over before submitting it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For reference, &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/talk/moraltext/MoralText.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here is my writing sample&lt;/a&gt;. It was a shortened version of the fourth chapter of my honors thesis. In my case, I might say that my writing sample helped get me into some of my programs as professors who I wanted to work with emailed me to tell me how they liked my sample and how it aligned with projects that they wanted to do. My point in mentioning this is to say that you should not simply select &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; paper to submit, but to think carefully about the research that you are trying to do in graduate school and have this paper be a reflection of those goals. This paper should, ideally, also demonstrate the potential that you have to the learn and apply some of the core research and statistical methods that you would need in your career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;CV&#34;&gt;CV/Resume&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your CV/Resume is your opportunity to showcase your experiences in and out of academia. While some of these experiences, most notably those related to research projects or teaching experiences, will be on your statement of purpose, activities that demonstrate transferable skills such as public speaking or leadership in clubs/sports might not be on the statement. That is why your CV is an important part of your application &amp;ndash; it helps to demonstrate your achievements but also show the diverse experiences that you had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, while your CV is a good place to describe campus jobs or co-curricular activities, it can also help make your case as a researcher to use the descriptions to demonstrate experience and competence with research, time-management, organization and communication related skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I quasi-templated my own CV that I used in my application to demonstrate possible sections that can be used in your own CV. It is available &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.overleaf.com/read/fmpwssrwrjsr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here on Overleaf&lt;/a&gt; in $\mathrm{\LaTeX}$ format. The PDF should be available for download and the format is easy to emulate in Word. For $\mathrm{\LaTeX}$ users, you are welcome to make a copy of the code and work off that copy for your resume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your CV is also a document that would take time and revisions. I highly recommend consulting a career coach in your career center or a professor for advice on ways to refine your CV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;LOR&#34;&gt;Letters of Recommendation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Letter of Recommendations are opportunities for others to make an impression on your behalf. Most applications will require 3 professional references from professors, supervisors, or other professional references &amp;ndash; in other words, not family or friends. For research-based Ph.D. programs, I recommend selecting recommenders who you know in either a research or teaching experience. This might be a Primary Investigator (PI) in a lab that you worked in or an instructor for a class that you were a Teaching Assistant (TA). They should know you fairly well and agree to write a good letter for your application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about your letter writers early and let them know that you are interested in asking them for a letter for graduate applications as early in the process as possible. As soon as you know which programs you are applying to, let your letter writers know of the deadlines and send them information on how to submit their letters. They might ask you to provide them with your application materials, so be sure to send that information to them in a timely manner so that they have ample time to prepare their letters (spproxinately 3-4 weeks before the deadline).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you hear back from your programs, be sure to let your letter writers know the results regardless of whether or not you were accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;SOP&#34;&gt;Statement of Purpose&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you google &amp;ldquo;How to write a (good) Statement of Purpose for graduate school&amp;rdquo; (or something to that effect), you will largely get blog posts or lists of ways to write a &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt; statement of purpose, or a list of things &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to do. The reason for this is that there is not necessarily a hard-and-fast recipe for writing a good statement of purpose but there are certainly many ways that you can do it wrong. When writing your statement of purpose, look at some of those! To put it quite bluntly, it is better for the internet to warn you in their list of don&amp;rsquo;ts than to be rejected from a program for these mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When reading your application requirements, many of them will just have a place to upload a statement of purpose without much else in terms of directions. However, some departments will specify what they want to see in terms of content, word count or page limits. Be sure to research these requirements and keep time in mind as you write you statement of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a general statement of purpose, it is best o limit it to 2 pages. Some good things to discuss in your statement can include any research plans that you have, career goals, past research experience, and why you want to attend graduate school, especially in the particular program in which you are applying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the process of writing the statement of purpose, it is helpful to get several people to review and revise your statement. It is a part of your application that may require the most time. Revising the statement with different input can help strengthen your writing, catch typos and provide insight on things to add or change. I recommend seeking a diverse group of people who might know you in different contexts to help with different components of the statement. Having a friend who knows your background or an advisor who knows your research look over your statement allows them to provide you with insight on how you can add or change pieces to put your best foot forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;OMS&#34;&gt;Opportunities for Minority Students&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve seen posts on Twitter and Facebook numerous times about how higher education inherently gives an edge to wealthy white individuals and application fees make this endeavor inaccessible for low income students. There are some things colleges/universities are doing to address the problem and this may help you in your application if you qualify.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Fee&#34;&gt;Application Fee Waivers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a member of an undergraduate research program for minorities such as McNair or SROP, or if you receive a Pell Grant from your FAFSA, you can qualify for application fee waivers to most of your programs. Be sure to look into these early on. Some schools are specific in how you can acquire a waiver and they might require additional materials in order to secure this waiver. You can often find instructions by simply conducting a google search of &amp;ldquo;[SCHOOL NAME] Graduate Application Fee Waiver&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Visit&#34;&gt;Diversity Visit Weekends&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some graduate schools also conduct diversity visit weekends. These are often full expense paid trips to visit a graduate program for a weekend &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; the application is due. To qualify for these, you would need to be from a diverse background as defined by the program. These opportunities allow you to network with members from the department that you are applying to, learn more about the application process and about graudate school in general, and provide you an opportunity to ask questions. These opportunities often come with application waivers to the school itself. Since most of these are in the Fall, applications are often opened and due in the summer beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some possible opportunities &amp;ndash; some of these are general, some are specific to Political Science. Please know that this is not an end-all list. In fact, I welcome contributions. Please &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/#contact&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;write to me&lt;/a&gt; if you know of any opportunities that fit this criteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Ohio State University &lt;a href=&#34;https://odi.osu.edu/graduateprofessional-student-recruitment-initiative-gps?fbclid=IwAR1o3RnfxrMqNU6vKA4dzFwuM82Dc2N_gBuIVh-LY_XhiHA3UxBtT3WpHVw&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Graduate and Professional Student Recruitment Initiative&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Purdue University &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.purdue.edu/gradschool/diversity/programs/graduate-diversity-visitation-program/?fbclid=IwAR31YFTkv1d-hvEX7ASU-AMuWMsNxneAENxJhWPTVQKmTx8NVM5SJGmJtVY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Graduate Diversity Visitation Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University of Michigan Political Science Emerging Scholars Conference (ask your Political Science Professor about this)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University of Wisconsin &amp;ndash; Madison Political Science &lt;a href=&#34;https://polisci.wisc.edu/commitment-to-diversity/diversity-recruitment-conference/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Diversity Visiting Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Northwestern University &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tgs.northwestern.edu/diversity/diversity-recruitment/introduction-to-graduate-education-igen.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Introduction to Graduate Education&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University of Illinois &amp;ndash; Urbana-Champaign &lt;a href=&#34;https://grad.illinois.edu/diversity/aspire&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aspire Illinois&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am always happy to answer questions that you might have. Please &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/#contact&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions about the process or want to make edits to improve this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you &lt;a href=&#34;https://jacklreilly.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Dr. Jack Reilly&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://amandafidalgo.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Dr. Amanda Fidalgo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When testing so last minute, think about whether it is necessary. It is best to plan for the GRE well in advance of your graduate applications.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to COVID-19, ETS is providing a temporary &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ets.org/s/cv/gre/at-home/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;online testing option&lt;/a&gt; through September 30, 2020.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic CV</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/academic-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/academic-cv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This template was made as a combination of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.overleaf.com/articles/vuong-v-trinhs-cv/rwjrnbbbtgdy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vuong V. Trinh&amp;rsquo;s CV&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/treyhunner/resume&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trey Hunner&amp;rsquo;s Resume&lt;/a&gt; while integrating additional bonus features&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like my &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/files/CV.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CV&lt;/a&gt;? I created this style based on the aforementioned inspirations so that my CV can be more organized with sections and subsections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;demo&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a demo of the template, see my &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/files/CV.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CV&lt;/a&gt; tab in the menu bar or consult the output from the published template below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;embed src=&#34;CV.pdf&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;800&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-this-template&#34;&gt;Using This Template&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To access this template, clone my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/LaTeXTemplates&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;$\mathrm{\LaTeX}$ Templates GitHub Repository&lt;/a&gt; and extract the CV folder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are three main files&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;CV.tex&lt;/code&gt; &amp;ndash; This is the main file where you write your CV contents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;CV.cls&lt;/code&gt; &amp;ndash; This is the class file that contains information about the parameters of the file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;head.tex&lt;/code&gt; &amp;ndash; This is the heading file that contains what would normally go before the &lt;code&gt;\begin{document}&lt;/code&gt; command &amp;ndash; new commands, packages and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; When using Adobe reader for PDFs, the section and subsection headers are labeled and thus can appear on the left-hand panel for easy cross-reference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Section Headings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; These follow the style in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/treyhunner/resume&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Trey Hunner&amp;rsquo;s Resume&lt;/a&gt; containing the title of the section followed by a line spanning the entire width of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subsection Headings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; These follow the style of the two-column style CVs such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.overleaf.com/articles/vuong-v-trinhs-cv/rwjrnbbbtgdy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Vuong V. Trinh&amp;rsquo;s CV&lt;/a&gt; such that the heading is on the left and the main text is on the right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Numbering Environment&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Allows for both forward and reverse numbering environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Websites using Academic</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/post/websites-using-academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/post/websites-using-academic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Academic theme on Hugo&lt;/a&gt; is quite a popular theme for people, especially academics to use to create their own websites, be it for a lab or as a personal portfolio page, like this one. And this is for a good reason. &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Academic&lt;/a&gt; is quite easy to use and it is very flexible to the needs of the user, allowing creators to design web pages using a variety of widgets and even allowing them to create some new ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, you may ask, why are you writing this post? Well, as the title suggests, there were a few things I learned that I wanted to document for my future self and for those wishing to pick this theme up. Many users have also done something similar, with great examples being from &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com/create-your-website-with-hugo/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;George Cushen, the creator of Academic&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://alison.rbind.io/post/2019-02-21-hugo-page-bundles/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Allison Hill, a coauthor on Blogdown&lt;/a&gt;. I should note that this post is not necessarily geared towards a setp-by-step on how to create a website using Hugo themes, as those tips are documented by the creators of the themes themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-wish-i-knew&#34;&gt;What I Wish I Knew&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s begin with the second question because I think it is more straightforward and something that people who want to use this theme should know &amp;ndash; &lt;em&gt;Academic is so simple, yet complex&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given the amount of documentation that Academic and their community of users provide on the internet, it is easy to understand the &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;simple&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; component. Academic relies on Markdown, or R Markdown if you would prefer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, the more complicated part comes with the organization of the site, which, for beginners, may come with a learning curve. I created my site using &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt;, but there are many ways that one can use to create and deploy an Academic site. But regardless of what you end up choosing, the first few hours, maybe days, would be dedicated to you constantly asking yourself: &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Where is that file?&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; The &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Blogdown book&lt;/a&gt;, which I recommend looking through if you choose Blogdown, suggests a 10 minute curve for users not familiar with code in CSS or JavaScript, but my personal experience showed that it took a lot longer for me to get accustomed to the site and framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the good news is that once you get over the learning curve, it is quite easy to edit and innovate your Academic site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-learned&#34;&gt;What I Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that this list was based on the structure of Version 4.9. I will continue to update this list as I learn more&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I discussed earlier, there can be a learning curve to the site. In the rest of this post, I will attempt to document all the tips I found handy in my process of getting accustomed to the site. In this process, I assume that you are using Blogdown and have &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;read the book&lt;/a&gt; to know how to &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/other-themes.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;initiate an Academic site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assuming you don&amp;rsquo;t already know Markdown, learn some basic syntax. Academic&amp;rsquo;s documentation provides a &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;great guide to do this&lt;/a&gt;. It also helps to have a general understanding of HTML syntax as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bookmark some cheat sheets. I recommend:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fontawesome.com/icons?d=gallery&amp;amp;s=regular,solid&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Font Awesome general (fas)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://fontawesome.com/icons?d=gallery&amp;amp;s=brands&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Font Awesome Brand (fab)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jpswalsh.github.io/academicons/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Academicons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.webfx.com/tools/emoji-cheat-sheet/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Emojis Cheatsheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.toptal.com/designers/htmlarrows/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;HTML Symbols Cheatsheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build your site often to see if there are errors. I recommend using the &lt;code&gt;blogdown:::serve_site()&lt;/code&gt; command, which, if you use R Studio, generates a preview in a viewer tab in your screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regardless of the approach you use to create and edit your site, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DO NOT TOUCH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; the &lt;code&gt;themes/&lt;/code&gt; folder in your site source. You can mirror the file structure under the &lt;code&gt;themes/&lt;/code&gt; folder to create your own content, as &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/page-builder/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;explained here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When building with Blogdown and deplaying to GitHub pages, I recommend using a two repository system where one serves as the &lt;code&gt;source&lt;/code&gt; and the other is the publish directory. This is because there are some challenges for GitHub pages to get along with Hugo.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; For this website, I have a source repository where I make my edits and publish it to my website directory (&lt;code&gt;lin-jennifer.github.io&lt;/code&gt;). You can use this system by adding &lt;code&gt;publishDir = &amp;quot;../USERNAME.github.io&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt; to your &lt;code&gt;config.toml&lt;/code&gt; file, where &lt;code&gt;USERNAME&lt;/code&gt; is your GitHub username.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unless you have a good reason for why you need the &lt;code&gt;.Rmd&lt;/code&gt;, use standard &lt;code&gt;.md&lt;/code&gt; files for posts. Additionally, Academic &lt;strong&gt;recomments that the &lt;code&gt;.Rmarkdown&lt;/code&gt; file extension be used for anything with R content&lt;/strong&gt; in lieu of &lt;code&gt;.Rmd&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When inserting things, it is probably easier to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/#icons&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Academic-specific shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; rather than standard Markdown methods of inserting images, videos, embeds and others. If you do use standard Markdown syntax, especially for images, place the content in the &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; folder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Patience.&lt;/strong&gt; Your site won&amp;rsquo;t update immediately after &lt;code&gt;update.sh&lt;/code&gt; tells you that it has been pushed to GitHub. It will take a hot minute&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-forward&#34;&gt;Going Forward&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I keep saying throughout this piece, there are many ways that one can use, create and edit Academic. If there is something that you know that would make editing and creating content easier, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/#contact&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;let me know&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this could be done using point-and-click in R Studio as well. Simply go to &lt;code&gt;File&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;New Project&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;New Directory&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;Website using Blogdown&lt;/code&gt; and select the options that you want, including &lt;code&gt;gcushen/hugo-academic&lt;/code&gt; in the theme field to signal Academic as your theme.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo provides some guidence on some different ways to deploy to GitHub Pages &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. However, the two repository system is what I see some users use and what I find to be the most straightforward.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCF Poster</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/ncfposter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/ncfposter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The poster template is based off the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.overleaf.com/latex/templates/uw-madison-poster-template/tfbyxyhbymsq&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;UW&amp;ndash;Madison Poster&lt;/a&gt; on Overleaf.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;demo&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outcome of the poster can be seen here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/NCFPoster/blob/master/main.pdf&#34;&gt;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/NCFPoster/blob/master/main.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/ncfposter.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-this-template&#34;&gt;Using this Template&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best way to use this template is to clone the GitHub repositiory in the link at the top of the post or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/NCFPoster&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you choose to delete some of the demo objects in the file in favor of your own materials, be sure to include the following items&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;main.tex&lt;/code&gt;: The root file that contains the temaplate for the poster seen in the demo. You can rename this to be whatever you like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;ncftheme.sty&lt;/code&gt;: Contains the code for the colors and the design that the poster needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Images/&lt;/code&gt;: This serves as the established graphics path and contains the New College logo for the top of the poster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCF (Mark)Down</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/ncfdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/package/ncfdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This template was made based off the style created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/holtzy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Yan Holtz&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/holtzy/epuRate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;epuRate&lt;/a&gt; template. Thank you for your inspiration and assistance in creating this template&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;demo&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See it in action here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/ncfdown/&#34;&gt;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/ncfdown/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-this-template&#34;&gt;Using this Template&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install this template using &lt;code&gt;devtools&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;library(devtools)
install_github(&amp;quot;lin-jennifer/ncfdown&amp;quot;)
library(ncfdown)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By downloading the package, the source for the template can be accessed by using &lt;code&gt;File&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;New File&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;R Markdown&lt;/code&gt; → &lt;code&gt;From Template&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;package-options&#34;&gt;Package Options&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this package, there are several options under the &lt;code&gt;output:&lt;/code&gt; category on the &lt;code&gt;YAML&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;ncf&lt;/code&gt;: This option provides a basic structure for HTML documents knitted out of an R Markdown document. Simply note &lt;code&gt;ncfdown::ncf&lt;/code&gt; under the output option to activate this template.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;ncfweb&lt;/code&gt;: Consult the &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/rmarkdown/rmarkdown-site.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;R Studio Handbook&lt;/a&gt; for how to create a website. This option provides a design for an R Markdown based website. It differs from the &lt;code&gt;ncf&lt;/code&gt; option in three ways:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Author and Date in footer only rather than under the title&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removes code folding option and code folding button on the upper-right-hand corner on each page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removes GitHub triangle in upper right-hand corner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To switch between the two versions of this package, simply edit the &lt;code&gt;YAML&lt;/code&gt; such that the one under &lt;code&gt;ncf&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;output:
  ncfdown::ncf:
    toc: TRUE
    number_sections: FALSE
    code_folding: &amp;quot;hide&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;would become this under &lt;code&gt;ncfweb&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;output:
  ncfdown::ncfweb:
    toc: TRUE
    number_sections: FALSE
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contributing-to-this-package&#34;&gt;Contributing to this Package&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help me improve this package, please reach out using the following methods:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jenniferlin2025@u.northwestern.edu&#34;&gt;jenniferlin2025@u.northwestern.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send a message via the &lt;a href=&#34;https://lin-jennifer.github.io/#contact&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; tab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open a pull request on the project GitHub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/ncfdown&#34;&gt;https://github.com/lin-jennifer/ncfdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Is and What We Can Be$:$ Using Social Norms to Influence Intergroup Attitudes and Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/norms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/norms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott, Nelson, DeSantis, Gillum &amp; Beyond$:$ A Look at 2018 Florida Precinct Returns</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/fl18vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/publication/fl18vote/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will God&#39;s Grace Guide My Vote?</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/religiousprimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/religiousprimes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask Only What Your Country Can Do for You$:$ Group Interests, Constituency Characteristics, and Demands for Representation</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/demands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/demands/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color, Size, and the Effectiveness of Direct Mail$:$ A Study on Voter Turnout in a Local Election</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/event/mail/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lin-jennifer.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
